allexciting.com 2019-05-30

# Site and Privacy Policy and Affiliate Disclosure

**This policy is effective from 22 May 2018.**

This privacy policy sets out how AllExciting.Com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.  
AllExciting.Com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

AllExciting.Com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### What we collect and why

AllExciting.Com do not collect any personal information. If you contact us via email or contact form, we will only use your email adress for answering your questions and then delete it from our system/mailbox when the conversation is ended.  
We will never give or sell your email adress to anyone.

**We use Google Analytics to collect demographic information such as country, city and interests.**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

To improve our products and services.  
To customize the website according to visitors interests.

**Google Analytics**

When someone visits allexciting.com we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns.

We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site.

This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.

If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this.

We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

_**Google automatically collect and store certain information** in their server logs which includes device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL, cookies that may uniquely identify your browser and/or your Google Account, in accordance with their data privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>_

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites, visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We or a third party contracted by us may use technologies such as cookies, Web beacons, or scripts to gather information about how you and others interact with our Web site.

For example, we will know how many users access a specific areas or features within our site and which links or ads they clicked on.

We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used, improve our marketing efforts, and provide content and features that are of interest to you.

From time to time we use Google AdSense to serve ads on this site.

When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites.

You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. The table below explains the cookies we use and why.

**Cookie** | **Name** | **Purpose**  
---|---|---  
|  |   
Universal Analytics (Google) | _ga  
_gali  
_gat_UA-1036645-1  
_gid | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website and WordPress blog. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website and blog, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited.  
|  |   
YouTube cookies | PREF*  
VSC*  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE*  
remote_sid* | We embed videos from our official YouTube channel using YouTube’s privacy-enhanced mode. This mode may set cookies on your computer once you click on the YouTube video player, but YouTube will not store personally-identifiable cookie information for playbacks of embedded videos using the privacy-enhanced mode.  
Read more at [YouTube’s embedding videos information page.](http://www.google.com/support/youtube/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=171780 "External link")

PREF – * Expires after eight months  
VSC – * expires at the end of your session  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE – *expires after eight months  
remote_sid – * expires at the end of your session  
  
|  |   
|  |   
  
## 

## How do I change my cookie settings?

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Find out how to manage cookies on popular browsers:

To find information relating to other browsers, visit the browser developer’s website.

Click to enable/disable google analytics tracking.

Click to enable/disable google webfonts.

Click to enable/disable google maps.

Click to enable/disable video embeds.

**Facebook Like,  Facebook Recommend, Facebook Share official buttons**

_We embed a Facebook widget to allow you to see number of likes/shares/recommends and “like/share/recommend” our webpages. This widget may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the widget, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the widget (such as “liking/sharing/recommending” our webpage), if you are logged in to Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy:<https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update>_

**Twitter Tweet official button**

_We use a Twitter Tweet widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Twitter’s servers for you to be able to tweet our webpages using your Twitter account. These requests make your IP address visible to Twitter, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy:<https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update>_

_We use a GooglePlus widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Google’s servers for you to be able to share our webpages using your GooglePlus account. These requests make your IP address visible to Google, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy:<https://policies.google.com/privacy>_

**Pinterest Save official button**

_We use Pinterest Save widget at our website to allow you to pin images to Pinterest from our webpages. These requests may track your IP address in accordance with their data privacy policy:  <https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy>_

**Reddit Badge official button**

_We use Reddit Badge widget at our website which  may log information when you interact with the widget. This may include your IP address, user-agent string, browser type, operating system, referral URLs, device information (e.g., device IDs), pages visited, links clicked, user interactions (e.g., voting data), the requested URL and hardware settings, in accordance with their privacy policy: <https://www.redditinc.com/policies/privacy-policy>_

**StumbleUpon Badge official button**

_We use StumbleUpon Badge widget at our website which  may log information when you interact with the widget. Log Data is a form of Non-Identifying Information, in accordance with their privacy policy: <http://www.stumbleupon.com/privacy>_

Click here to add your own text

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Affiliate Disclosure – Income to keep the site up

Costs for keeping the site up, operate with research and travel are paid by the commissions given when someone book hotels, tockets or tours at the site.

### Disclaimer

Naturally, there is no guarantee that the locations or hotels visited are perceived by you in the same way, or that there haven’t been changes.

We shall not be responsible for possible written errors in AllExciting.Com, or changes that may occur in the programs of events, or otherwise. See organizers’ websites for any updated information before ordering your journey.

Anyway, we will always do our best to always collect and submit correct information, and strive to give the best service as possible to you.

### Contact

For any quesions or other contact, use our [Contact Form by clicking here >>](http://allexciting.com/contact/)

Scroll to top
